Spirits take no prisoners
Red Sands is a action, horror, war film directed by Alex Turner.
A group of U.S.
soldiers on a mission in the Middle East find themselves
with nothing to do in their free time.
Out of sheer boredom they end up destroying an old statue in
the desert, only to unleash a horrific entity.
Jeff Keller, played by Shane West.
Marcus Howston, played by Leonard Roberts.
Trevor Anderson, played by Aldis Hodge.
Gregory Wilcox, played by Callum Blue.
Chard Davies, played by Brendan Miller.
Tino Hull, played by Theo Rossi.
Red Sands is a 2009 American horror film directed by Alex Turner and written by
Simon Barrett, in their second collaboration following Dead Birds.
The film stars Shane West, Leonard Roberts, Aldis Hodge, Theo Rossi,
Callum Blue, Brendan Miller, Noel Gugliemi, and J.K.
Simmons, and introduces Mercedes Mason.
The tone is dark.